-
Forgive me, you embrace me in vain
You're right
When you ask me about all those things
But though it hurts my pride
I'll just pile it all on top of each other.
Thank you for watching.
You hang on to me, don't you?
I know you hang on to me for your own reasons.
I'll do the same for you, I'll do the same for me
You make it so easy
It's been great today.
Popping like lately
Dweepriper
Forced to ask bye bye
Even if you cry from an idiot
I'm the beautiful moon
Jara, stop it!
You're the best, you have a big, clumsy body.
Nice time to get in on the act by pretending to be white
I can't get enough of you
I am more Alshai than me
I always feel like this
I am the best, but I'm still Louiqa
The best, the best, the best
This party this all
Stand up in faces
There's no time like the present Space, but who I am is what I'll be
A.D.B.D. Like a kiddy heart
We can make it!
We can make it
You're wicked, aren't you?
My sister! Hey!
Hey! Let me stay!
Maybe you're the strongest, Poppy.
I'm not gonna pretend I'm weak Fight!
I don't even know about longing
I don't know what I'm like
I don't like it. Stop it.
Strongest is a big, clumsy hotel...
I can't go on with you, I can't go on with you
I can't go out with you
I'm more in love with you than I really am
I always keep my dream
Isn't it the best
HOKUTEN's masquerade work is made up
I'm coming for you, I'm coming for you, I'm coming for you, I'm coming for you
Just freeze, don't scream
I'm going to die!
It's so big, it's a job!
And the most powerful!
He's the most powerful man in the universe, even if he's a jibber-jabber.
It's always the girls who lead the way
You're the strongest, too.
You may be jittery, but you're still the strongest in the universe.
Harosse! This time I'll be talking with Reina Yokoyama from Morning Musume。
and Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume。 24.
This time, we'll be bringing you the story of the two of them!
Today, November 27, is the release date of Morning Musume。 24's new album
Professionals 17.
This album is their first original album in 3 years and 8 months.
It's the first original album released in 3 years and 8 months, and there's a lot to choose from!
Koibito is a very Morning Musume-like song, but there are also some cute songs, cool songs, unit songs, and so on.
Haruka Inoue, do you have any song recommendations?
I participated in a unit song for the first time as an original member.
The song "I'm glad I got to meet you" is a unit song with Rena Yokohama, and I'm very happy to have had the opportunity to participate in it.
But it's the first time for me to sing in a unit song.
I had a hard time remembering the lyrics because there are more places to sing than when we all sing together.
Please listen to the album as much as you can!
The autumn tour will be held at Yokohama Arena on December 6!
Morning Musume。24コンサートツアー秋ウィーキャンダンスブロウェルドAyumi Ishida Final is the only one!
This is the last tour with Ms. Ishida.
I, Yokoyama, have been trying to imitate Ms. Ishida's way of laughing.
It's been eight years since I joined the group, but I've been doing it for quite a long time.
Mr. Ishida has a very distinctive way of laughing.
He laughs with his whole body, and it's very funny.
When I tried to imitate her, it turned out that we were quite similar.
Whenever Yumi Ishida performed in Sendai, her hometown, we would talk about how much we looked alike.
I used to do it at the end of every show when Yumi Ishida performs in Sendai, her hometown, but recently it's not so popular anymore.
But recently, it wasn't getting any traction.
I stopped doing it because it wasn't popular anymore.
But this tour is the last one for Yumi Ishida, so I wanted to do it for this tour.
And there were two shows in Sendai, right?
I wanted to do it at one of them, but I couldn't because there was no MC.
So I still have some things to do, so I hope I can do it before the last show at Yokohama Arena on December 6.
I hope I can do it before the last Yokohama Arena concert on December 6.
I might be doing it at Yokohama Arena Park.
In that case, I'm really sorry.
But it is one of my memories with Mr. Ishida.
So I'm spending my time thinking that it would be nice if we could do that somewhere.
Now, please take a look at this video.
Here you go.
Lulu!
Rei, Yume, Ria, Ichikawa, Okazaki, Sakira, Akari, Mifu, Tanaka, Hiroho, Hanashi, Sana, Kajun, Yuriya, Hana, Yume
Yes, yes
Yes, er, let's do it with the four of us with a good feeling until Risachi's share.
Let's show everyone who came to the Budokan what we can do, and let's do it in high spirits.
Yes, We are JETS!
Please do so.
Three, two, one.
Here we are.
Thank you very much.
Kids' figures!
It's got so much power.
Amazing.
I'm so motivated!
I'm so excited.
There's really only a limited number of us.
I don't even know if I'll be able to stand next time.
I would like to come to the next concert that I would like to have Budokan again.
I'll do my best.
I'm nervous if I have more opportunities to show off my skills.
The more I have to show off, the more nervous I get.
I was more nervous in rehearsals at first.
I was still more nervous during rehearsals.
But now that I'm having too much fun, I've stopped being nervous...
I'm going to enjoy the show while keeping my mind tight.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to be overflowing!
Ready?
It's coming true!
Tomorrow
Wow.
Why is your voice starting to shake?
You're good at it, Rikkchan, so just keep it up.
You keep it up.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best
As always
Yes, sir
We are
Chuchuuus
Change h organizers
Hot
in the wind
expensive
JuJu SuFaTour 2024 Triangle of Two Special
Let's get excited about Budokan!
Your love is something that I love
I love you, I love you, I don't love you
Side Mirror Street at Midnight
I don't love you, I love you
Tokyo tonight
Radio, it's coming true.
Rain forecast for tomorrow.
Stop work. Why are you depressed?
Because I'm not in love. I'm the real me.
I can't leave you alone
I can't leave you alone I can't leave you alone
Love Story When you're out of it, around the next corner
Temptation, Love & Joy, you're going to get it.
Anxious Hands, Sleepless Love, Get out of the Passenger's Seat
Let's go see a new morning with a new me
Graduation Let the wind gently blow your hair back
Classic, plastic, tenderness
I love you, I don't love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I don't love you, I love you, I love you
Make you
GPS, it's spilling
I'm full of right, but it doesn't hurt
I'm so excited for the time you gave me
I can't go to hell for that, I can't stop breathing
Expression Love and Joy in Profile
Someday we'll be piling it up
Things discussed with kindness and things that have faded away
The result, how many times, will be a bond, a dream and a lie.
gradations, it wasn't you, that's all.
I can't help it. I'm drunk on the excitement.
I'm laughing at the five-star rating.
Aiming for the most stars
Expression, Predictable Love & Joy.
Here, I'll change it for you
Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal Heart to steal
Get out of the passenger seat
Goodbye, my love
It's so clear, I'm not going back
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Classic!
Classic! Classic!
I'll always be here for you! Keep up the good work!
This is Reina Yokoyama from Morning Musume。 24 and Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume。 24.
Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。 24 presents "Halo! STAY!" from here on.
Project members. Project members
Project members' behind-the-scenes and behind-the-scenes stories.
Project members' behind-the-scenes and behind-the-scenes stories. Behind the scenes.
Have you seen it?
Yes, I have.
It's really good, isn't it?
The members are so serious.
It's a project where you can see the members as they are, without any flaws or insincerity.
It makes me happy as a member.
So one day we might be in close contact with them.
I think it would be interesting to have a close contact with this member.
Is there anything you'd like to see us do?
Here it is.
This?
For sure.
That's for sure.
It's the kind of vibe you only get at Haloste.
I thought you'd be interested in Haloste.
I thought you might be interested.
You're right.
I've never seen anything like it.
You mean behind the scenes of this MC.
From the meeting, sure.
I guess it depends on the members.
Meetings...
Yokoyama and I are so noisy.
From the meetings.
But the serious ones...
I wonder if they have meetings silently...
So this time, we're going to see Yumi Ishida, Hamare Okamura, and Rio Sakurai of Morning Musume。 24 in Taipei for the interview.
Yumi Ishida, Hamare Okamura, and Rio Sakurai, who are going to interview in Taipei.
Good morning.
What are you working on today?
Well, I have some interviews and performances today.
Yesterday, I was just talking with fans.
But today is a real job.
It's a full day, so I'm going to do my best.
I think it was the first time for both of you to be overseas, and yesterday was like being a manager for a day, but it's the first time for me to do an interview.
I'm nervous.
Do you have any suggestions from your seniors?
I would like to hear.
But the presenter who will be taking care of us today speaks very good Japanese, so I don't think we have much to be nervous about,
But if you are thinking of writing an article or something, it's easy to understand.
Indeed.
If I were in Japan, I might not have a good vocabulary today, but that might be enough to convey the message in an easy-to-understand way.
I understand.
I was wondering, did you think about the formation today?
Yes, I did. We discussed it a little yesterday, but of course, there is no other dance formers who can perform brave dances with only three dancers.
We made a special position for today and danced a little more than usual.
I would like to dance a brave dance with the feelings of the 10 members in Japan.
For example, what part of the dances are you doing that you don't usually do?
The interlude chart usually increases, starting with me.
Then, Reina-chan, Oban.
I was the first to start dancing. I am usually the last. I am the last.
One in front. That's right.
But from there.
What do they say? Like, "Dance from there.
A little earlier, earlier.
I think I can handle it. Somehow, it's going to be good.
We have a dance leader here, so he can teach us. I'll be fine. You can teach me.
I won't be able to see the performance, so please take care of me. Okay, I understand.
Okay, I'll give it back to you first. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Do you have your own routine before PR activities?
When I do PR activities, or when I am asked to interview someone about a song, I look at the lyrics first.
I am often asked which song is my favorite or what was the most memorable lyric. So I prepare for that.
I have some kind of throat lozenges that I put in my mouth.
Mm-hmm.
Like a sheet.
Yeah, it's like really thin.
And you put it on the top of your mouth, what do you call it?
I don't know what to call it.
I do that a lot during performances.
I do it during performances, but I also do it at individual events and when I'm doing PR for the show.
We talked a lot.
I don't often get a chance to drink water.
I feel like it's good to put that on the wall, so I do it.
I feel like it's good to put it up.
Thank you very much.
Do it! Do it! Just do it!
I can't! I can't! It's been too long.
I don't want to tell anyone the secret of my sigh.
I don't want anyone to know why I'm short on eyes.
No, no, no, no, I can't even tell a robot!
This is the first time Sakurai Ryu-chan and I have come to Taiwan.
But in words, in texts, in messages...
I had received warm words from everyone.
But we have never met in person.
I wondered if there were really people overseas who would support us.
I was a little anxious, but
But we were really happy to have about 200 people come and visit us at the Hot Up Shop.
came to the Hot Up Shop and talked with us.
and talked with them.
I felt so much support from them.
I was so happy
I was so happy.
Welcome to Taiwan!
Thank you very much for your visit.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
This is my first visit to Taiwan.
As much as possible
Because it is my first time in Taiwan
I want to experience
I want to be impressed by what I see for the first time.
Thank you very much.
I have not done a lot of research
I didn't do a lot of research.
I've done a certain amount of research on what's necessary and what's famous.
I saw the city.
Wow! There are a lot of motorcycles.
Or, "There are suddenly tall buildings in the cityscape.
or "This is the kind of desk I have when I have a meal.
I was impressed by many things
I was very impressed by many things.
There are three songs in this album.
What shall we do now?
I'm going to do a live radio show.
Is it starting yet?
I think it's already started.
It's time for us to get in the middle of it.
Thank you very much.
I'm Koch.
I'm Kochi. Take a break.
I'm opening the show now.
Okay.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, thank you very much.
It's the last job for today. Shu is right.
Hot pot, hot pot, hot pot.
I'm sure I've seen you on the radio before.
Did you steal any techniques from him? This is Mr. Ishikawa.
Chemo war...
Do you say it? Say it.
Well, there is an announcement section at the end.
I'll give a reply there.
He didn't say anything.
After I was told at the beginning that I could say more at that time...
I've been saying "ai" and "ai" and "ai" and "ai" and "ai.
Uh, so, uh, uh...
I'm looking forward to hearing from you all.
The mood address is
morning at mark 1422 radio nippon
We look forward to hearing from you!
what's up!
and
we'd like to get some.
Because a few of them will create a pause for the next announcement.
That's for sure.
I've been practicing it a lot.
I'm looking forward to seeing you today.
Today, too.
I'm giving you a different verbal cue.
You're right. I don't know how they'll take it.
All I have is love for food.
I don't love to eat.
I don't know if I love to eat or love to eat
Listen to the song by Andely Pucelli and Aline!
This song is a great earthquake song.
The current time is 8:14 pm.
This is the娛樂時代 of the Chinese New Network.
Morning Musume 24
Please say hello to everyone.
My name is Kangseong Yutaka.
I'm Kangseong Yutaka.
Yay!
Next.
I am Injilian.
Yay!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to Sacrizer!
There's more stuff below!
My favorite one
Sweet potato dumplings
Sweet potato and taro
Tapioca
Do you eat tapioca?
I just had some and I'm over it.
Are you okay now?
I'm fine.
See you in the next video.
Chillin'. Cheese, cheese, cheese.
We just finished recording the radio show!
How was it?
DJKEN was really kind and talked to us a lot in Japanese, and we were able to relax and answer his questions, so it was a lot of fun.
We had a lot of fun because we were able to relax and answer his questions.
We really didn't expect to be on live TV for our first promotion in Taiwan.
It was really a wonderful experience. Thank you very much.
What were some of the challenges of working overseas?
Were there any difficulties in your job, or any points that you tried to work out that you felt were difficult?
I think it was difficult to speak in Japanese, but when I spoke in Japanese, I smiled more clearly than usual and used my face to communicate.
Like using your face to communicate.
Yes, I did.
I did that.
I tried to use the Chinese I had learned as much as possible.
I try to speak using the Chinese I've learned as much as possible.
Um...
billing
Please take care of me.
Ma-ba-na-na...
Ma-ba-na-na-na...
By using the words you have learned
I was able to communicate
I was very happy
I was very happy.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I enjoyed watching you two today.
Wow!
I couldn't believe I was working here for the first time, I was having so much fun.
Hey.
Yes.
I was a little worried about them, but I wondered if they were okay.
But I think the Taiwanese people are really kind,
Even during the press conference and the cabinet meeting, whether they understood my Japanese or not, they were very kind to me.
I was impressed by their smiling faces and nodding in agreement, whether they understood Japanese or not.
I thought it was easy for me to talk with him, and I think it was the same for them.
Do you have any expectations for the two of them, or do you have any strict advice for them?
Well, I have one thought.
This is something I have to be aware of when I do interviews in Japan,
There are a lot of punctuation dots.
I have to be aware of this when I do interviews in Japan, but there are too many punctuation points in my stories,
First, we went to eat hot pot.
Ko-po, I thought this was delicious.
I thought I should be able to respond in sentences that use that circle.
Have you ever been told that?
I'm sure you have. That's normal in Japan, isn't it?
That's what Mr. Kitagawa told me.
You can't do that unless you are conscious of it, so I was conscious of it again today.
I think it was the last overseas job for graduating seniors.
How was it?
I was selected as one of the three in Taiwan, so I did not spend three days longer with Mr. Ishida than everyone else,
So I felt like I was lucky at that point.
In interviews, I always say that I want to make a lot of memories before graduation, but I really feel like I am making memories and it was like a graduation trip, so I was very happy. Thank you very much.
You were blowing steam, weren't you?
I thought so.
It's on fire.
Yes, it was my first time to work abroad, and I never thought I would be one of the two in your last work abroad...
I didn't think I could be one of the two, so I was very happy.
I am sad to know that you are graduating again, but I am also very happy to hear what you said.
I would like to do my best to inherit what you have said.
I thought I was able to circle here once.
I thought, I thought, I thought...
He's already gone.
You have just seen Morning Musume・24 members Ayumi Ishida, Takashi Okamura, and Rio Sakurai on their way to Taipei for an interview.
Yes, so you are working overseas.
This is the first time for me to go abroad since I joined Morning Musume。 I also went abroad for the first time since I joined Morning Musume。
I had never been abroad before.
I had never been abroad before, but after joining Morning Musume。 I had never been abroad before, but since I joined Morning Musume。
I had never been abroad before, but since joining Morning Musume。
Haruka-chan has never worked overseas, but I'd like to go.
I wonder what it's like not to speak the language.
Well, yes, it's a bit nerve-wracking, but the food, the foreign food...
I've never eaten foreign food before.
I've never tried it before.
I'd like to try it.
It would be really fun if we all go together.
Like eating together.
We should all eat a lot of food together.
Let's definitely go.
Let's go!
Okay, that's all for now.
Please look forward to the next Halobihan!
Harostei
Rena Yokoyama of Morning Musume。 24 and Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。
and Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。
Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。
From here, we would like to talk a little about each other.
I, Yokoyama, will ask you some questions.
So, Haruka Inoue, don't think too much and just answer quickly and at your own pace.
Okay?
In reference to the "Ochokochochochoina Fantasia Romance" from The Professionals' 17th album.
Who's the first member that comes to mind when you hear the word "ochokochochocho"?
Haruka Inoue.
What's the most impressive thing that happened during the current fall tour?
When my costume got caught in my hair and I couldn't take it off.
Haruka Inoue, 18 years old. What are you most interested in now?
A straw that has a delicious and colorful thing inside it for drinking milk.
How do you spend your days off?
I go to the cinema.
There are only 9 days left until the finals of Bloweld Ayumi Ishida. Tell us about the impressive words that Ms. Ishida said to you.
She told me that it was fine for Haru-san to be Haru-san.
It's the end.
Thank you very much.
Your answer was very smooth, but there were a few things that bothered me.
First of all, an impressive event in the current fall tour
Her hair gets caught in the costume.
Once when I had to paint the top of my costume.
And I thought, "Wow, I can't take it off.
Yes, it did. I got it off in the end.
Yes, I was able to take it off, but it was a bit frustrating.
You never know what's going to happen at a concert.
Suddenly, a hair gets caught or something.
I don't know where it came from, but it came in front of me.
It happens, doesn't it?
That kind of thing happens, you know.
That's part of the fun of being at a live performance.
And what is it that Haruka Inoue, 18, is most interested in right now?
I asked you one more time.
There's a straw that tastes like milk when you drink it.
Is there such a thing?
It's like a sweet bead in the straw.
What?
There is such a thing, but at first I thought there were only strawberry, chocolate and vanilla flavors.
But today I found a straw with a very colorful flavor, and I thought it was amazing!
They are cereal flavored. Cereal flavored and colorful? Cereal flavored and colorful?
Wow, that's amazing. I didn't know that existed. I'm curious.
Oh, so you drink one with milk?
You stick it in your milk and drink it, and then your milk tastes like cereal, or strawberry milk, or something like that.
That's so awesome!
Am I the only one who doesn't know about this?
I'll look into it. Later.
Wow, you answered so smoothly, it was perfect.
Thank you very much.
Questions for Mr. Yokoyama after the VTR.
Hallo! STE!
Reverse! Wenever! JOHNSON!
Humanity is all alone.
Tears are all transparent
Today, too, the strongest and the most dexterous body!
Morning Musume。24 New Album Professionals 17th NOW ON SAION
Hallo! STE Then I would like to ask Yokoyama-san a question.
Yes, I'll do my best to make it smooth. From the titles of the songs on the Professionals 17th album, what is the most annoying thing that happened to you recently?
I was pissed off because the junior members of Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。's junior members are too cute.
What is your secret story about The Professionals 17th? What's your story?
My room is very dirty now.
What was your most memorable moment with Haruka Inoue?
No matter where I put my hand, Haruka Inoue sticks to me.
What do you do on a rainy day?
I leave the house no matter what.
Only 9 days to go until the final of Emi Ishida Full Wield!
What is Ishida-san to Yokoyama-san?
He is a master of laughter!
Oh!
Yay!
What was my most memorable moment with Inomeharka?
Yes! When I put my hand out to her.
She would put her hand on me like this! First of all, isn't this cute! But what's more...
But you don't have to put it here! For example, even if it's really high up, she'll do her best to get on it like this.
When I put it upside down, she even tried her best to do it upside down. She's so cute, and the other day, in between shows, there was Haruka Inoue, and she was pretty far away from me.
I saw Haruka Inoue, and I thought she was pretty far away from me, but I saw her eyes, so I did this from a long way away and she ran like this.
And then she came running and she was so cute that I thought it was so cute that it made me feel so relaxed.
I was really healed by that, and that made a big impression on me.
What do you mean? Well...
Your hands smell nice.
I'll help you. Okay. I'll try to take better care of them on a daily basis.
And one more thing...
Mr. Ishida, for you, Mr. Yuka-yama, Mr. Mushida is a master of laughter, and I've told this to Mr. Ishida himself.
Mr. Ishida is always funny, even with them... he's always chatting and laughing.
And he is funny during mc, but he also has a natural sense of humor.
When he stands in front of the fans during the live, the god of laughter comes down to Mr. Ishida.
You can do the kind of laugh that can't be done by thinking.
For example, a little funny hubbling, or just hanging a towel on the stage during a live performance.
It's not the kind of fun you can do with a high
I think he is loved by laughter, and I respect him a lot in that aspect.
I'm so glad you enjoyed this episode. We'll be right back with more after this.
We'll be right back with our last song, "Let's Tower.
weather n shoot
rar
weather n shoot rar
το Kraft
ți
Susie
Laughing that I see the goal Laughing that it's not the goal
Let's still look for it
Wow Wow Wow
If I believe in it, it will come true I wish for you and the blue sky
I can't believe I made it this far
Wow Wow Wow Wow
I've always been lost at the crossroads
Baby Baby Baby
I'll be with you tomorrow
How many years has it been?
How many times did I almost lose?
I was always on my own.
Maybe we're turning the corner here.
Or maybe I'm just tired.
Maybe it's up to me.
I was alone in the corner of the room
I counted the smiles and the tears
And if the smiles are just a little bit bigger
If it's big enough, the world will shine brighter.
I'll take that!
Everywhere I go, I cry
I held on to the thought that there's no finish line
I looked up at the clouds
Wow, wow, wow
Worrying about where tomorrow's gonna be
All I could see were the memories
I could go on and on and on
Wow, wow, wow
Regret's not falling down at the crossroads
Baby Baby Baby
Tomorrow's that way
Hey!
Wherever you go
I'm not giving up.
Hey!
Let's sing it together
No matter how far
Hey!
Let's run
Towards the finish line
Smile and say you see the finish line
Smile and say it's not the goal
Let's keep on searching
Wow, wow, wow
Wishin' on you and the blue sky
I've made it this far
Wow Wow Wow Wow
Crying where's the finish line
Crying that there's no finish line
I looked up at the clouds
Wow Wow Wow
Wondering where tomorrow will be
All I could see were the memories
I could still go on
Wow, wow, wow
Wondering where tomorrow's gonna be
All I could see were the memories
I could go on and on
Wow, wow, wow
Wishin' for you and the blue sky
I could go on and on
Wow, wow, wow
Where's the intersection where you didn't fall down
Baby Baby Baby
Which way is tomorrow?
Tomorrow we'll be together
Tomorrow we'll be over there
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Wow. Wow.
Wow. Wow. Wow.
Thank you.
Wow Wow Wow.
Thank you very much for today.
It was a choo-choo!
Thank you so much to everyone who came to JuiceJuice Concert Tour 2024 Triangle B2 Special.
Thank you so much for watching the live streaming on Hulu and the live viewing at movie theaters.
I was really happy that so many people were able to see the show. I was very happy that so many people were able to see our performance at the Nippon Budokan.
How was it? Eva from the Cute Team: Yes, the performance itself was really great.
Well, the performance itself went by so fast, and I was so happy that I still feel like I was dreaming,
This time we had a lot of time to change our clothes and get ready,
I had a lot of time to change my clothes and get ready, so I was able to change my hairstyle quite a bit,
It was also a performance that I had never experienced before,
It was a great experience for me, and most of all, it was a lot of fun,
I also thought the JuiceJuice family was wonderful.
It was great. Thank you very much.
The A-active team performed "This is Destiny,
How was it, A-chan?
This time, the A-Active team.
During the rehearsal, I was told repeatedly that I should be pissed off,
I didn't understand at first. I didn't understand at first. But then I thought, "Well, I don't know.
But I was like, "Let's make everyone get excited with our enthusiasm! I was getting more and more competitive,
I have the feeling that we have created something that is incomparable to what we did on the first day of rehearsals.
I really hope you will watch it again and again.
I really want you to see it again and again.
It was really cool.
Thank you very much.
Next, let's continue.
If it's a fashion day.
Yes, I think so. No, but we would like to play Cute's Passionate Ecstasy.
That's right.
Yes!
That's right. That's right.
We had ℃-ute's song covered at the Budokan this time, and when we watched the rehearsal video together after rehearsal, the lighting was really cool.
When we watched the rehearsal video together after rehearsal, the lighting was really cool.
I was really happy to see that, and the three of us were talking about it as if we could say, "This is our favorite song, and it's passionate.
We danced to "Passion and Passionate Ecstasy," and it was really fun to see everyone's happy faces.
Thank you very much. This is the 2nd Triangle Groove, so it's been 6 years since the first Triangle Groove.
It's been 6 years since the first Triangle Groove 2, so it's been 6 years since the first Triangle Groove.
I hope you could feel the cute, active and passionate part of JuiceJuice at the live.
I hope you can feel the cute, active, and passionate side of JuiceJuice at the live.
I hope you enjoyed the Budokan concert!
Please continue to support JuiceJuice!
That's all for now, this is JuiceJuice!
Bye bye!
Reina Yokoyama from Morning Musume。 24 and
Haruka Inoue of Morning Musume。 STE, presented by Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume。
It's time for us to say goodbye.
How have you been so far, MC?
I'm always nervous about MC, but it all happened so fast.
It went by so fast that I'm feeling a little sad.
But I'm sure you had such a good time.
Yes.
I don't really talk much with other Morning Musume。 I didn't get to talk much with other Morning Musume members, so it felt fresh.
It was a lot of fun talking with you like this.
Here's an announcement!
Morning Musume。24's new album Professionals 17 was released today!
It's an album with a lot to offer!
This is the last album with 13 members, so please listen to it a lot!
And on December 6th, Morning Musume。24 Concert Tour Autumn will be held at Yokohama Arena.
We Can Dance Blow Weld Ayumi Ishida Final Concert Tour will be held at Yokohama Arena on December 6.
It will be the culmination of the fall tour and Ayumi Ishida's graduation live.
All the members will do their best, so please watch out for us!
And Morning Musume。24AngelBeyons will perform on Countdown Japan 2425!
Morning Musume 24 will perform on December 30, and Angstrom and Beyons will perform on December 29.
Hello Project 2025 Interfaces Kakuto 5 will be held on January 2 next year!
This will be my second concert in the winter.
This will be my second concert with Hello Project.
I don't know what kind of concert it will be yet, but I'm looking forward to enjoying it again this year.
I'm looking forward to having fun again this year, so please come and enjoy the concert!
I'm looking forward to seeing you this year.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating and subscribe to our channel!
I'll be playing with Reina Yokoyama from Morning Musume。 24 and
Haruka Inoue from Morning Musume。 24.
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!